Lloyd: So now that you've completed
session two of unit two it's
time to complete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
So if you open your assessmen booklet
and scroll down to section two, which
is Understand Current and Emerging
Challenges in Cyber Security, you
will see that there is only one
learning objective in this section.
To meet that learning objective, the
question has been split into two.
And for question 1A, it's asking
you in the table below, give at
least two examples of current
challenges in cyber security.
So 1, 2 there.
And then for question 1B, it's asking
you to give at least two examples of
emerging challenges, so challenges
that are up and coming and are going
to be a challenge in the future.
Once you've done that, you can
then save your assessment booklet
and move on to session three.